hsabank.com 2010-12-17

# 

                                       The Webster Financial Corporation Privacy Policy and Disclosure
                                                HSA Bank is a division of Webster Bank, N.A.
The directors, management, and staff of                including termination in appropriate cases.             purposes such as processing transactions,
Webster Financial Corporation, and its family                                                                  mailing and auditing services, providing
of companies (“Webster”) respect and                   We have established and continually main-               information to credit bureaus and responding
protect the privacy of our customers’ person-          tain security standards and procedures to               to court orders and legal investigations. We
al financial information.                              help us protect you from unauthorized                   collect and use personal information to
                                                       access to confidential nonpublic personal               administer our business and deliver quality
This disclosure is made on behalf of Webster           information that Webster maintains about                service to you. This may include advising
Financial Corporation and its family of                you, including through the Internet.                    you about our products or services, those of
affiliated companies: Webster Bank, N.A.                                                                       our affiliates, those of our business partners
(including its divisions, HSA Bank, Webster            Accuracy and Right to Correct Your
                                                       Account Information                                     and other opportunities that we believe may
Investment Services and Webster Financial                                                                      interest you.
Advisors); Webster Business Credit Corp.;              We continually strive to maintain complete
Webster Capital Finance, Inc.; Fleming,                and accurate information about you and your             INFORMATION SHARING
Perry & Cox, Inc.                                      accounts. Should you ever believe that our              The foregoing information about both current
                                                       records contain inaccurate or incomplete                and former customers may be shared with
We understand that our customers furnish               information about you, please notify us. We             the following categories of Webster compa-
private information to our companies in the            will investigate your concerns and correct              nies and unaffiliated third parties:
course of daily business, and we are commit-           any inaccuracies.
ted to treating such information responsibly.                                                                  Sharing Within Webster’s Family of
We know that our customers expect privacy              INFORMATION COLLECTION                                  Companies (“Affiliate Sharing”)
and security for their personal and financial          At Webster, we collect, retain, and use                 For our everyday business purposes,
affairs.                                               information about you for the purpose of                information we have collected may be
                                                       serving your financial needs and administer-            shared among Webster’s family of compa-
We take steps to safeguard private informa-            ing our account relationships. We collect               nies (for example, Webster Bank, N.A., and
tion that has been entrusted to us by our              information we receive from you on applica-             Webster Capital Finance, Inc.) in order that
customers. When we use information, it is to           tions or other forms like surveys and ques-             we can provide products and services
help serve you better. Your information helps          tionnaires (for example, loan applications,             appropriate to your needs and circums-
us appreciate all the business you have with           deposit account applications and requests               tances. Federal law gives you the right to
our companies and identify affordable                  for information about accounts or products              limit (called an “opt-out”) Affiliate Sharing of
products and services that might serve you             and services). We also collect (i) information          information about your creditworthiness. To
better. The following privacy policy and               about your transactions (such as payment                Opt-Out of Affiliate Sharing of Creditworthi-
disclosure outlines our practice regarding             histories or account balances) with us or               ness Information see Section 1 under Your
personally identifiable financial information          experiences (such as information you have               Choices below.
(or “nonpublic personal information”) for              communicated to us about your financial
consumers, those consumers who become                  needs) with us, (ii) information we collect             Limiting Marketing to You By Webster’s
our customers, and our former customers.               through “cookies” (information collection               Family of Companies
                                                       devices from a web server) and (iii) informa-           Federal law gives you the right to limit some
CUSTOMER PRIVACY BILL OF RIGHTS                        tion we receive from consumer reporting                 but not all marketing from the Webster family
At Webster, any employee access to cus-                bureaus about your credit history and                   of companies. Federal law also requires us
tomer information is authorized for business           creditworthiness.                                       to give you this notice to tell you about your
purposes only and is based on the sensitivity                                                                  choice to limit marketing from the Webster
of the information and our employees’ or               USE OF INFORMATION                                      family of companies. You may limit the
agents’ need to know. We remind employees              We use personal information in ways that are            Webster family of companies, such as
regularly of their obligations regarding               compatible with the purposes for which we               Webster Bank, N.A., Webster Capital
customer information. Disregard of these               originally requested it. For example, we use            Finance, Inc., Webster Business Credit
obligations will result in disciplinary action,        the information for our everyday business
                                  Consumer Privacy Preference Form
No action is required if you do not want to opt-out or limit sharing information. If you want to opt out or limit, check any/all of the following boxes and
mail this form to:
                                                              th
HSA Bank, A Division of Webster Bank, N.A., 605 North 8 Street, Ste. 320, Sheboygan, WI 53081 or call 1-800-357-6246
 Do not share information about my credit worthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business.
 Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
   If you have previously completed a consumer privacy preference form, all preferences remain in place and there is no need to complete
                                                                    an additional form.
Customer Information: To enable us to process your request, please complete the following:
Last Name                                                            First Name                                                                Middle Initial
Address                                                              City                                                State                 Zip
Type of Account           Account Number
Date                      Signature
zixbypass

                                         The Webster Financial Corporation Privacy Policy and Disclosure
                                                  HSA Bank is a division of Webster Bank, N.A.
Corp., and Fleming, Perry and Cox from                        Customer Privacy Preference Form pro-                Guard your social security number.
marketing their products and services to you                  vided with this disclosure.                          Do not release information to people
based on your personal information that they                                                                         you don’t know, especially over the
receive from other Webster companies. This               The Customer Privacy Preference Form                        phone or Internet.
information includes your income, your                   must be mailed in a separate envelope and                 Review bank statements for accuracy.
account history, and your credit score.                  should not be included in any other corres-               If you are denied credit for no apparent
                                                         pondence. We will process your request as                   reason, obtain a copy of your credit re-
Your choice to limit marketing offers from the           soon as possible after we receive it.                       port.
Webster companies will apply until you tell
us to change your choice. To limit marketing             Information Reported to Consumer                     If You Become a Victim of Identity Theft
based on such information received from                  Reporting Agencies                                        Contact your bank and all others with
other Webster Companies, see Section 2                   Under the Fair and Accurate Credit Transac-                 whom you have a financial relationship.
under Your Choices below.                                tion Act (FACTA), you have the right to notify            File a police report if you have a loss.
                                                         us if you believe we have reported inaccu-                Report the fraud to the major credit
Sharing with Webster’s Service Provid-                   rate information about your account to any                  bureaus:
ers/Joint Marketers                                      consumer reporting agency. Such notices                            Equifax                      1-800-525-6285
From time to time, we may use outside                    should be sent in writing and include your                         Experian                     1-888-397-3742
companies to perform services for us for our             complete name, current address, social                            Trans Union                   1-800-680-7289
everyday business purposes, reporting to                 security number, telephone number, account
credit bureaus and to assist us in marketing             number, type of account, specific item of               For additional help, call the Federal Trade
our own products and services. In order to               dispute and the reason why you believe the                   Commission at 1-877-ID-THEFT
complete these tasks, we may provide our                 information reported is in error.                                 or visit their website at:
service providers with information we collect                                                                        http://www.consumer.gov/idtheft/.
about you. We require our service providers              Send your notice to: Webster Financial
to comply with our standards regarding                   Corporation, P.O. Box 10305, WFD730,
security and confidentiality, and permit them            Waterbury, CT 06726. We will investigate
to only use your information for purposes                your concerns and correct any inaccuracies
                                                         and confirm our actions to you. You may              The Webster symbol is a service mark of
authorized by us.                                                                                             Webster Financial Corporation. Webster and
                                                         obtain a free credit report annually by calling
Webster may also enter into joint marketing              Equifax, Experian and Trans Union at the             Webster Bank are registered in the U.S. Patent
agreements with selected financial institu-              numbers listed in this brochure.                     and Trademark Office.
tions, in order to assist us in providing quality
products and services to you. We require                 At Webster, we have no higher priority than          Webster Bank, N.A.
                                                         continuously earning our customers’ trust.           June, 2010
these financial institutions to keep your
                                                                                                              Member FDIC
nonpublic personal information confidential,             Identity Theft
and permit them to only use your information             Identity theft is a growing crime in our                               DISC_Privacy Policy_4444_060110_V1
for purposes authorized by us.                           country. Each day, thousands of people
Your Choices                                             become victims of identity theft. Identity theft
1. To Opt-Out of Affiliate Sharing of                    occurs when someone steals your personal
          Creditwothiness Information, check box         information and uses it to establish credit,
          number 1 on the Customer Privacy Pre-          charge items or borrow money using your
          ference Form provided with this disclo-        name.
          sure.                                          Protecting Your Identity
2. To limit marketing based on personal                      Tear up unused credit offers and other
          information received from other Webster              documents containing personal
          Companies, check box number 2 on the                 information before you discard them.
                                    RE: FINANCIAL PRIVACY
Dear HSA Bank Accountholder:
HSA Bank is a division of Webster Bank, N.A., and part of a large and diversified financial organization. Webster Bank brings to HSA Bank significant
strengths and resources, which help HSA Bank to improve its services to you.
As part of Webster Bank, we follow the Webster Financial Corporation Privacy Policy and Disclosure. Under this Privacy Policy and Disclosure, you
retain significant rights concerning the sharing of your nonpublic personal information.
We have a strong commitment to safekeeping your information. Our current practice is that we do not share your nonpublic personal information with
certain affiliates of Webster Bank. These affiliates include Webster Investment Services, Inc.; and Fleming, Perry & Cox, Inc. As a result, these affiliates
are not able to use your nonpublic personal information to send you solicitations for any products or services. You may, however, request information for
products and services from these affiliates at any time.
You also have the right as a HSA Bank accountholder to prevent the sharing of your nonpublic personal information with all affiliates of Webster Bank.
To do so, you can call our Client Assistance Center at 1-800-357-6246 or complete and mail the attached Consumer Privacy Preference Form to the
address indicated in the Form.
Sincerely,
Kirk Hoewisch
President, HSA Bank
zixbypass
